A Guide to the James Branch Cabell Collection
University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library, #5518
James Branch Cabell Collection 1956-1957
University of Virginia. Library. Special Collections Dept. Alderman Library University of Virginia Charlottesville, Virginia 22903 USA
5518
12 items
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1957 Dec 23
Container List
- Correspondence
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1956 Nov 6; TLS, 1 p. w/env.
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1956 Dec 3; TLS, 1 p. w/env.
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, with annotated booklist, 1956 Dec 12; TLS, 2 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 Jan 18; TLS, 1 p. w/env
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 Jan 28; TLS, 1 p. w/env.
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 Feb 16; TLS, 1 p. w/env
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 Mar 25; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 Apr 1; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 Apr 9; TLS, 1 p.
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 May 1; TLS, 1 p. w/env.
  - James Branch Cabell to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 Sep 3; TLS, 1 p.
- Miscellaneous
  - Notes on James Branch Cabell's books which he sent to Matthew Bruccoli, 1957 Apr 1 and 9; Typed book lists, 5 p.